Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
The message of worshipping God Alone
is... there's a big
switch
this year. This marks
a new era
and the switch is from the religious leaders
like the Pope
and Jewish leaders and Muslim
leaders
to
Academia, the Academic people
who include Jews, Christians, and Muslims
and who will look at the
data
of the Quran objectively
and then they will tell the world
adding the credibility of academic research
and they will tell the world about it. This is what's happening this coming year.
Yesterday,
we had the president of the... the vice president of the biggest Islamic university in Saudi Arabia and three of his people
come here and discuss
the matter of worshipping God Alone.
And you know all their arguments.
But one thing happened that stands out
that I don't think I or you will ever forget
and it's something that I don't think Satan himself will dare do.
That man objected to having this on the wall by itself.
He wanted Muhammad next to it.
He, instead of, being pleased with seeing the name God on the wall, he actually criticized it.
I mean, unbelievable as this may be, we have a sign on the wall out there saying Happiness is Devotion to God.
And that sign pleases all the believers in God including Jews, Christians.
And the hardcore Jesus worshippers are even pleased with it and they call us and they tell us how much it pleases them in the morning to drive by and see it
or in the evening, but this man was upset to see
the name of God Alone up there.
These people worship Muhammad
just like the Christians worship Jesus. I mean, they're all human beings and they're all victims of Satan the same way.
I want to read for you some of the writings about Muhammad.
Actually, I don't wanna do that because it's kind of crazy, but I'd rather concentrate on our positive data, but since I opened the page, I will read just a couple of things to give you an idea. Then, it will get to our good results.
OK. It says here that in the beginning...
The title is the creation of the greatest RUH or spirit.
And it is the light of our master and prophet Muhammad. This is what they're saying Peace and blessings be upon him.
It says here Then God, Allah TA'ALA, looked at that light again and it sweated from modesty before God.
From the sweat of its nose, God created the angels.
This is now the light of Muhammad.
From the sweat of its face, He created the throne.
Poor God didn't have a throne to sit on until the light of Muhammad sweat on the face.
Oh, He created the throne, the foot stool,
the tablet of forms, the pen, the sun, the moon, the whales and the stars and what is in the heavens.
OK
From the sweat of its breast, He created the prophets, the messengers, the ULUMA (religious scholars).
No wonder!
The martyrs and the SALIHUN. That is the righteous people.
This goes on and on. OK. From the sweat of its back and from the sweat of the two eyebrows,
He created the community of Muhammad and the Muslims both men and women.
We're all created from the sweat of the brows, eyebrows of Muhammad.
There's a part here.
Oh
Then, God created... this is... then, God commanded all the souls of creation to look at the form of Muhammad. And so they looked at it.
Whoever saw his hand became a Khalifa (ruler and Sultan among creatures). I don't want my name in there.
Whoever saw his forehead became a just prince.
Whoever saw his eyes became one who preserves the word of Allah. It goes on like that.
Whoever saw his lips became a cabinet minister.
Whoever saw his nose became a doctor.
Whoever saw his mouth became one who fasts.
Whoever saw his teeth became one who is beautiful of face among men and women.
I'm gonna skip here. Whoever saw his neck became a merchant. OK.
Whoever saw his breast became a 'A'LEM. a scholar.
Whoever saw his abdomen became one who does RUKU and SUJUD. prostration
By the way, they skipped from here down.
They didn't say whoever saw...
Whoever saw his feet became a hunter.
Look at this Whoever saw his shadow became a singer.
There's another place here. Whoever saw his fingers became a scribe. Whoever saw his fingers of his right hand became a tailor
and Whoever saw his left hand became an ironsmith.
Whoever saw his left palm became a Meiser.
Whoever saw his back... the back of his right hand became a cook.
Do we have any cooks here?
Whoever saw his right palm became a money changer and embroiderer. Whatever the relationship is.
Whoever saw his left palm became a corn measurer.
You know the corns that grow on your toes. NO.
It says, Oh, whoever saw his throat became a MO'AZZEN (a person who calls to prayer).
There is some place where somebody saw some finger and became a carpenter and so on.
But this here. I'm gonna close with this. This is ridiculous but...
Whoever saw nothing became a Jew, Christian, or a Zoroastrian or a KAFIR. disbeliever. So,...
There are no carpenters among the Jews. There are no tailors among the Christians. This is nonsense, a bunch of nonsense.
And this man had the goal to say why do you have God Alone, on the wall?
Now, we just get to the serious, positive work that we're doing. I was visiting with my brother in California last weekend.
And we checked some of the results of the research, generally. He got hold of the index to the Quran and we looked up a few words.
I just want you to be the most familiar with this great great miracle. God calls it one of the greatest miracles
which will show you that when you read the Quran, you are reading God's message to you.
And that which will give you full confidence that not just any human being wrote the Quran and is fooling you
or that his statements are not reliable or trustworthy.
You will have full confidence. So, I'm gonna keep informing you, keeping you up-to-date with this information.
My brother looked up the word Quran
and, in the index of the words of Quran which counts every word and is proven to be correct except as far as the word... the number of the word ALLAH is concerned where they made
the same mistake that the computer made. You know about that. But he found that the list says 58.
But in SURAH number 10, there is one statement that says the disbelievers would say: give us a Quran other than this one.
So, you remove that. Minus 1 and the mentioning of Quran is 57. 19 x 3.
When you take the numbers assigned to the chapters and the numbers assigned to the verses where this word is found,
the total is 2660 which is a multiple of 19.
19 times 140.
And then we looked up the word messenger.
And he found that in the index, the total was 116.
You see, when the person who doesn't know and looks at this say well, this number is not a multiple of 19
but one of these 116 times is a messenger of Pharaoh in chapter 12.
The messenger of Pharaoh went to Joseph to ask him about the dream of the king. So, you remove that.
The other, so... the other..... another RASUL is mentioned in the last two verses of SURAH 9.
So, there are 2 of them that you remove and you have the total of 114.
OK. These are things that you should be familiar with. 19 times 6.
And then we looked up the word WAHED or one
and it said 25, but 6 of them had nothing to do with God and that God is One is mentioned in the Quran 19 times and you take the numbers assigned to the chapters and the numbers assigned to the verses
and they add up to a total which is a multiple of 19.
So, I will let you absorb this much which was repeated before and think about it as we all repent and ask God to forgive us and help us along His right path. Tooboo Ela Allah.
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
We praise God and we bear witness that He is the only Lord and Savior.
There's only One God.
Well, Lisa Spray continues to make discoveries and I wanna share with you. She wants to share with us, what she found out lately by adding...
making additions of the verses and SURAH numbers. This is what God wants to teach us now that the numbers assigned to the verses
and the numbers assigned to the chapters are dictated by God Himself. They are not human-made.
Also, the sequence of the chapters as we have it.
Miraculously, the sequence of the chapters has nothing to do with the sequence of revelation of the chapters.
As you know, this is very simple and you're gonna remember it and see how everything in the Quran is Divine, is not human-made.
We have a missing Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem in chapter 9.
There is no Bism Allah.
And we know that this is made up in chapter 27.
There's been a 0 Bism Allah, and here there are 2 Bism Allah.
And you know that when you count the SURAHs starting with number 1 here and ending here, you have 19,
19 SURAHs between the missing Bism Allah and the extra Bism Allah.
There's an opening Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem in this SURAH and then in verse 30,
we see the queen of Sheeba sending a letter to Solomon and the letter was In the name of God, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful. Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem in verse 30.
Now, very simply, any of you can go home and do this. Add 9+10+11+12+.....+ up to 27. The total is 342. 19 x 18.
Now, see, why did God eliminate the Bism Allah from this chapter and put it in this chapter?
This particular series of numbers, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, up to 27. When you add them up, they give you this total. 342.
But this is half the story. It turns out that these two BISM ALLAHs are in the opening, let's say verse zero, and then you find the extra Bism Allah in verse 30.
The number of words... You count the words between the two Bism Allah and it is this number.
How do you like that?
I mean, it's a design that nobody can dream of.
The number of words between the two Bism Allah.
So, this is all I want you to.... NO! There is one more thing. It's just so much....
I was talking to Ismail Barakat in Canada today and he used the word that I can't remember. It is not explode. But he said the miracle is exploding.
I'm gonna remember the expression he used which was perfect. But this is what's happening now. It's really a blessed explosion to overwhelm the world
and to show how blind the top religious leaders are. The man who objected to having the name of ALLAH on the wall, God by Himself,
is, if there's a Pope in Islam, this is the second man. He's vice president of the top Islamic university and he knows nothing about the miracle.
In fact, they were so pitifully ignorant. I didn’t even want to open the discussion on it or say anything about it
and interestingly they didn’t wanna talk about it and they didn’t attack it which tells me that there are some quarters in Saudi Arabia that discovered the truthfulness of the miracle and told these people.
So, they don't wanna discuss it and for the first time they never attacked it.
They didn’t say Bism Allah is so many letters or...
was the first time... Never saw it... It's really.... I learned a lot by discussing the matters with them.
The other thing that Lisa wrote down here
was the number of verses from the first Quranic initials,
A.L.M. in SURAH 2, verse 1.
You count the verses. This is a huge number now.
You add up the verses all the way to the word nineteen in the Quran.
That's right. You know what I'm gonna say.
And the total is 5515.
Now, there are many angles to this miracle
and one of the things that the miracle does not ignore is the Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheems that are at the head of the SURAHs.
Now, between this verse (2:1) and this verse here which is 74:30
there are 71 Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem and when you add these,
the total comes to 5586 or 19 x 294.
The Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem is recognized as un-numbered verses.
And they are counted. When you add all the verses of the Quran including the 112 un-numbered Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheems, the total is a multiple of 19.
It is 6346. Right. This is 19 x 334.
This is the total number of verses in the Quran including all the Bism Allah, 112 of them.
There are a few more items that I would like to talk to you about, but we're running out of time, so I would mention one more item
that came across the... via satellite. We have one of our people in Morocco. His name is Yaghoobi Kamal and he called
and he read from this Muslim Perspective of September 1986, Muharram, 1st, 1406
where... I have consulted the Quran and the message was loud and clear, after seeking refuge in God from Satan,
that I wrote this. I said almost all present governments in the region will reject and scoff at this offer.
I had sent... if you recall, I had sent letters to every president and every king of every Muslim country in the world,
Arab and Muslim country and I invited them with evidence to form a United Islamic Nation.
And when I consulted the Quran, I will show you the verse in SURAH 9 by the way, that say do they not see that they're put to the test once or twice a year?
And this caused me to add this consequently, there will be a change of government in that region at the rate of at least 3 governments every 2 years.
Cause once or twice a year means 3 every 2 years.
Until a government comes with the specific objective of joining the United Islamic Nation.
Now, this looks like a flaky thing to some people,
but this turns out to be true. Exactly, two years after the publication of this statement,
Habib Bourguiba, the president of Tunisia was removed and a new president was.... a new government was installed and this happened next to... next door to our brother Kamal.
So, he fell. We had 3 governments fell. The government of Sudan, president Nimeiry, remember him?
and the government of Yemen, president Mahmood Ali
and finally, the last....the third one was president Bourguiba of Tunisia.
Now, those dictators... the only.... the most important thing.... the only thing, they care about in life is their throne,
their government, and the only thing that will make them do anything or move at all is to feel that their throne is threatened.
It's the only way, they'll do anything.
They also act as if they will live forever. They all do.
And they never learn from their past experiences. But I want you to be aware of this and I find it very interesting
that in the 2 years, we did have 3 of those governments. By the way, those governments were named. I did name the governments that received that letter.
So, we'll see what happens. I'm gonna write it in the new Perspective. I'm gonna ask the question who's gonna be next?
and I'm going to mail it to all the presidents and kings of that area.
So, May God guide us all and help us to be in His Kingdom.